<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UME PAL</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>

    <string name="checkout">Checkout</string>


    <string name="Myaccount"><b><t></t>My Account</b></string>
    <string name="editprofile"><b><t></t>Edit Profile</b></string>
    <string name="productdetails"><b><t></t>Product Details</b></string>


    <string name="user_name">eddy551</string>
    <string name="email_id">eddyok9@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="my_buying">My Buying</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="action_bar_heading">Explore</string>
    <string name="scrollbar_fade_duration">100</string>

    <string name="app_title">1000Days</string>
    <string name="baby_title">Baby</string>
    <string name="myAccount_title">My Account</string>
    <string name="all">ALL</string>

    <!-- Custom Bar Action Back Button -->

    <string name="heading_confirm">Details</string>
    <string name="clear_all">Clear All</string>

    <!-- HOME PAGE -->

    <string name="Medium_text">Medium Text</string>
    <string name="price">$34.90</string>

    <!-- LOGIN PAGE -->

    <string name="login_email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_fname">First Name</string>
    <string name="login_lname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="login_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="login_password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_forgot_password">forgot password?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_to">Login to</string>
    <string name="login_with_fb">Login With Facebook</string>
    <string name="login_signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login_signup_for">Sign Up for</string>

    <!-- FORGOT PASSWORD PAGE -->

    <string name="forgot_pswd_cancel_text">cancel and back to login page</string>
    <string name="forgot_pswd_reset">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_pswd">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_pswd_token">TOKEN</string>
    <string name="forgot_reset_pswd">Reset Password</string>


    <string name="title">Explore</string>

    <string name="APP_ID">842207449165732</string>
    <string name="promotion">Promotion</string>
    <string name="Categorynew">New</string>
    <string name="type">Types</string>
    <string name="baby">Baby</string>
    <string name="nointernet">No Internet</string>

    <string name="product_description1">In Annie Tiang TCM, Prof Joseph Yap and his team utilize techniques and treatments passed down through many generations and traditions. These traditions date back to nearly three hundred years ago</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splashscreen">Splashscreen</string>

    <string name="Pay_Now">Pa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_loginactivity">Loginactivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_forgotpassword">Forgotpassword</string>
    <string name="title_activity_signupactivity">Signupactivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_loginwithfacebook">Loginwithfacebook</string>
    <string name="title_activity_logoutpopup">Logoutpopup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>




    <string name="termsandconditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">Edit_profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile_pic">Edit_profile_pic</string>


    <string name="facebook_app_id">993399600701319</string>

    <string name="no_notification"> There are no notifications to display!! </string>
    <string name="notification">Notifications</string>

    <string name="available_at_store">Available at store pickup</string>

    <string-array name="quantity_values" >
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--NAVIGATION DRAWER + EXPANDABLE   -->

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
<!--
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item >\tSearch</item>
        <item >\tMyAccount</item>
        <item >\tBrowse</item>
        <item >\tShopping Cart</item>
        <item >\tNotification</item>
        <item >\tOrder History</item>
        <item >\tInvite Friends</item>
        <item >\tMembers</item>
        <item >\tCustomer Support</item>
        <item >\t\t\tContact Us</item>
        <item >\t\t\tGeneral terms</item>
        <item >\tLogOut</item>
        <item >\tLogin</item>
    </string-array>
-->

    <string-array name="new_nav_drawer_items">
        <item >\tBrowse</item>
        <item >\tShopping Cart</item>
        <item >\tReal Time Payment</item>
        <item >\tMy Account</item>
        <item >\t Wallet</item>
        <item >\tNew Referee</item>
        <item >\tNotification</item>
        <item >\tOrder History</item>
        <item >\tInvite Friends</item>
        <item >\tCustomer Support</item>
        <item >\t\t\tContact Us</item>
        <item >\t\t\tGeneral terms</item>
        <item >\tLogOut</item>
        <item >\tLogIn</item>

    </string-array>


    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>

    <!--Shopping Cart-->
    <string name="currency">SGD </string>
    <string name="dollar">$</string>

    <!--Shipping Address popup-->
    <string name="full_name">Full Name *</string>
    <string name="street_address">Street Address *</string>
    <string name="unit">Apt/Suite/Unit(optional)</string>
    <string name="state">State(optional)</string>
    <string name="country">Country *</string>
    <string name="city">City *</string>
    <string name="postal_code">Zip/Postal Code *</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone *</string>
    <string name="continue_shopping">CONTINUE SHOPPING</string>
    <string name="ship_to">Ship to: </string>
    <string name="info">* indicates a field is required</string>
    <string name="singapore">Singapore</string>

    <!-- Product detail-->
    <string name="store_address">Xminds Info \nAyurveda College Jn \nTrivandrum</string>

    <!-- Product detail-->
    <string name="uploadICpic">Pleace Upload \nYour IC photo</string>

    <!-- Wallet -->
    <string name="top_up">TOP UP</string>
    <string name="upgrade_membership">UPGRADE\nMEMBERSHIP</string>
    <string name="total_available_balance">Total Available Balance</string>
    <string name="total_lebadger_balance">Total LeBadger Balance</string>
    <string name="rebates">Rebates</string>
    <string name="commissions">Commissions</string>
    <string name="wallet_price">$ 15.40</string>
    <string name="rebate_statement">Rebate Statement</string>
    <string name="month">March 2016</string>
    <string name="rebate_gotten">Rebate gotten via own spending</string>
    <string name="commissions_statement">Commisions Statement</string>

    <!--RETURN POLICY-->

     <string name="return_policy">
   <![CDATA[
    <html><body><p style="text-align:justify">
    You may return all products within 7 calendar days of delivery (Please
safe keep your delivery receipt) if your product received falls under
one of conditions below:-</p>

<p>1. Product received is not product listed on lufluf by merchant</p>
<p>2. Product is not authentic and considered to be counterfeit products</p>
<p>3. Damage on the product that you received which due to manufacture
defect or damage incurs by delivery.</p>

<p>You can initiate your return/refund process by simply tap on contact us
and email to us via email address indicated. Please attach with clear
photo/s as possible and we aim to process all requests within 72 hours
upon receiving. Refunds are issued back to the original form of payment
used to purchase the order.</p>

<p>In the event, any form of voucher/gift card is applied to an order, and
that if order is refunded for any reason, any voucher/gift cards used in
that order will not be refunded.</p>

<p>At this time, Banyan Tree Ventures cannot refund, reimburse, cover, or
otherwise be responsible for any fees not paid to Banyan Tree Ventures.
This includes any customs taxes or VAT, as well as any return shipping
costs you may incur in the refund process and potential payment handling
fees.
   </p></body></html>]]>
   </string>

   <string name="terms_condition">
        <![CDATA[
    <html><body><p style="text-align:justify">
      <h> lufluf Terms Of Service<h></p>

<p><B>Terms of Service</B></p>

<p>These “Terms of Service” explain the contractual agreement between
you &#40;&quot;you&quot;, &quot;your&quot;&#41; and Banyan Tree Ventures Pte Ltd. &#40; &quot;Banyan Tree
Ventures&quot; ,&quot;<a href="http://qiito.com.sg">qiito.com.sg</a>&quot;, &quot;BT Ventures&quot; , &quot;lufluf&quot; , &quot;we&quot; ,
&quot;us&quot; , &quot;our&quot; &#41;, regarding your use of and access to our mobile app “luf
luf” (hereafter referred to as the “App”), and any resources,
features, functionality, or services made available through the Website
and/or App (hereafter referred to as the "Service"). Banyan Tree
Ventures reserves the right at any time and in its sole discretion to
modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Website, the App
or the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree
that Banyan Tree Ventures shall not be liable to you or to any third
party for any claim or loss related to you and arising out of such
modification, suspension, or discontinuance of the Service.</p>

<p><B>Acceptance</B></p>

<p>Your access to and use of the Website and/or App signifies that you have
read, understand and agree to be bound by these Terms of Service,
whether you are or are not a registered user of lufluf, and is subject
to your compliance with these Terms of Service. Banyan Tree Ventures
reserves the right to change, add, or delete any portions of the Terms
of Service from time to time, without liability or prior notice to you,
and your continued use of the Website and/or App constitutes your
acceptance of and agreement with any and all such changes. It is your
responsibility to regularly check the Website or App to determine if
there have been changes to the Terms of Service and to review such
changes. If you do not agree to abide by these or any future Terms of
Service, please do not access or use (or continue to access or use) the
Website or App. In addition, Banyan Tree Ventures may post additional
terms, conditions, rules or requirements related to the Website and/or
App and/or the services and features of either. All such terms,
conditions, rules, or requirements are or will be incorporated by
reference into these Terms of Service and you agree to be bound by and
subject to them. At its sole discretion, Banyan Tree Ventures also may
offer other services or features governed by different Terms of Service.</p>

<p><B>Customer Care</B></p>

<p>We strive to offer the best customer service for all of our users on
lufluf. Please feel free to contact lufluf Support at
<a href="support@qiito.com.sg">support@qiito.com.sg</a> with any questions or concerns and we will be
happy to help!</p>

<p><B>Refunds & Returns</B></p>

<p>We want you to be completely satisfied with your purchase on lufluf.
If for any reason you are unhappy, please contact lufluf support at
<a href="support@qiito.com.sg">support@qiito.com.sg</a></p>
<p>You may return all products within 15 calendar days of delivery (Please
safe keep your delivery receipt) if your product received falls under
one of conditions below:-</p>

<p>1. Product received is not product listed on lufluf by merchant</p>
<p>2. Product is not authentic and considered to be counterfeit products</p>
<p>3. Damage on the product that you received which due to manufacture
defect or damage incurs by delivery.</p>

<p>You can initiate your return/refund process by simply tap on contact us
and email to us via email address indicated. Please attach with clear
photo/s as possible and we aim to process all requests within 72 hours
upon receiving. Refunds are issued back to the original form of payment
used to purchase the order.</p>

<p>In the event, any form of voucher/gift card is applied to an order, and
that if order is refunded for any reason, any voucher/gift cards used in
that order will not be refunded.</p>

<p>At this time, Banyan Tree Ventures cannot refund, reimburse, cover, or
otherwise be responsible for any fees not paid to Banyan Tree Ventures.
This includes any customs taxes or VAT, as well as any return shipping
costs you may incur in the refund process and potential payment handling
fees.</p>

<p><B>Users</B></p>

<p>lufluf provides users the Service, including various media sharing and
communication tools, personalized and other content, and e-commerce. You
understand and agree that the Service may include advertisements and
that these advertisements help enable lufluf to provide the Service.
You also understand and agree that the Service may include certain
communications from lufluf. By using the Website, App or Service, you
will be automatically deemed to have opted in to receive e-mail
communication from us. When you sign in for the first time, your
preferences will be set to automatically publish all social interactions
to other social networks. However, you will be able to edit these
preferences at any time under “Settings”.</p>
<p>Any user IDs, names or passwords associated with your account shall be
maintained by you as confidential and should not be shared by you with
anyone not authorized to have access to your personal information. You
may have multiple accounts on lufluf but lufluf strictly forbids the
use of multiple accounts for the same sole user or the use of one
account for multiple users for the purpose of earning more rewards. luf
luf will not honor rewards from such accounts.</p>

<p>Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new feature or functionality
that augments or enhances the current Service, including the release of
or access to new properties, shall be subject to the Terms of Service.</p>


<p><B>Age Verification</B></p>

<p>By registering as a user, you certify that you are 13 years of age or
older. Children under the age of 13 may not become a lufluf user, and
parents or legal guardians may not agree to these Terms of Use on their
behalf. If you are a resident of a state, province or country that
imposes additional or different age requirements for disclosure of
personally–identifiable information, by registering as a user, you
hereby represent that your registration as a user, the provision of your
personally-identifiable information to us, and our use of such
personally–identifiable information as stated in our Privacy Policy,
does not violate the applicable laws or regulations of such state,
province or country.</p>


<p><B>User Communication</B></p>

<p>lufluf has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor, decline,
edit or remove all or a portion of any postings, submissions or content
in lufluf&#39;s sole discretion. By using the Website, the App or the
Service or communicating with lufluf or others by means of your access
to the Website or App, you consent to receive communications from luf
luf, including but not limited to, emails, text or Facebook messages,
and other online, mobile, or conventional methods as exist now or may
exist in the future. You also agree not to misuse the communication
tools available to you by means of your access to the Website or App,
including but not limited to, spamming, spoofing, sending unsolicited
commercial or other messages, and otherwise sending content that
violates the Terms of Service.</p>
<p>Privacy</p>
<p>By using the Website, App or Service or becoming a registered user, you
agree to be subject to the terms and conditions set forth in our Privacy
Policy as below:-</p>

<p><B>Privacy Policy Scope</B></p>

<p>This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way Banyan Tree
Ventures uses and protects the information we collect about users. All
use of Banyan Tree Ventures’ products and services, as well as visits
to our websites, are subject to this Privacy Policy.</p>

<p>The Information We Collect, How We Collect It, And How We Use It.</p>

<p>We may collect different types of personal and other information based
on your use of our products and services.</p>

<p>Some examples include:</p>

<p>Contact Information that allows us to communicate with you &#45;&#45; including
your name, address, and e&#45;mail address;</p>
<p>Equipment, Performance, Banyan Tree Ventures Websites Usage, Viewing and
other Technical Information about your use of our network, services,
products or websites.</p>

<p>We collect information in two primary ways:</p>

<p>You give it to us when you login with your Facebook credential;</p>
<p>We collect it automatically when you visit our websites or use our
products and services.</p>

<p>We may use the information we collect in a variety of ways, including:</p>

<p>Providing you with the best user experience possible;</p>
<p>Providing the services you use, and to respond to your questions;</p>
<p>Communicating with you regarding service updates, offers, and
promotions;</p>
<p>Delivering customized content that may be of interest to you;</p>
<p>Addressing network integrity and security issues;/<p>
<p>Investigating, preventing or taking action regarding illegal activities,
violations of our Terms of Service or Acceptable Use Policies.</p>

<p><B>Online Activity Tracking</B></p>

<p>We collect information about your activity on Banyan Tree Ventures
websites for a number of purposes using technologies such as cookies,
user behavior, and server log files.</p>
<p>We use that information to help tailor the content you see on our site.</p>

<p><B>Information Sharing</B></p>

<p>With Banyan Tree Ventures Products: Subject to applicable legal
restrictions, Banyan Tree Ventures products may share your Personal
Information with each other to make sure your experience:</p>

<p>Is as seamless as possible;</p>
<p>Benefits fully from what Banyan Tree Ventures has to offer.</p>

<p>In Other Circumstances: We may provide Personal Information to
non&#45;Banyan Tree Ventures companies or other third parties for purposes
such as:</p>

<p>Responding to 911 calls and other emergencies;</p>
<p>Complying with court orders and other legal process;</p>
<p>To assist with identity verification, and to prevent fraud and identity
theft;</p>
<p>Enforcing our agreements and property rights.</p>

<p>Additionally, when you complete a purchase with Banyan Tree Ventures’
lufluf service, we share your submitted shipping address and phone
number for shipping purposes only. This information is shared with the
entities fulfilling and shipping your order, such as the merchant and
the shipping provider.</p>

<p><B>Anonymous &amp; Aggregate Information</B></p>

<p>We collect some information on an anonymous basis. We also may anonymize
the personal information we collect about you.</p>
<p>We obtain aggregate data by combining anonymous data that meet certain
criteria into groups.</p>
<p>We may share aggregate or anonymous information in various formats with
trusted non&#45;Banyan Tree Ventures entities, and may work with those
entities to do research and provide products and services.</p>

<p>Safeguarding Your Information: Our Policy on Data Protection and
Security</p>

<p>We do not sell your Personal Information to anyone for any purpose.
Period.</p>
<p>We maintain information about you in our business records while you are
a user, or until it is no longer needed for business, tax, or legal
purposes.</p>
<p>We have implemented encryption or other appropriate security controls to
protect Personal Information when stored or transmitted by Banyan Tree
Ventures.</p>
<p>We require non&#45;Banyan Tree Ventures companies acting on our behalf to
protect any Personal Information they may receive in a manner consistent
with this Policy. We do not allow them to use such information for any
other purpose.</p>

<p><B>Links to/from Other Web Sites</B></p>

<p>Banyan Tree Ventures is not responsible for the practices employed by
websites linked to or from our website, nor the information or content
contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from
our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in
effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including
those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s
own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before
proceeding</p>

<p><B>Changes to Our Privacy Policy</B></p>

<p>If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those
changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect,
how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes
to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</p>

<p><B>Ownership</B></p>

<p>The Website, App, and the content and all intellectual property rights
included in or associated with the Website or App, including, but not
limited to patents, copyrights, trademarks, service marks, logos, are
either owned by lufluf or owned by others and licensed to us. All
rights, title and interest in and to the Website or App and such Content
remains with us or our licensors. Additionally, you may not remove or
alter any copyright, trademark, or other intellectual property or
proprietary rights notice or legend contained on the Website, App or in
the Content. You agree not to access the Service by any means other than
through the interface lufluf provides via the Website or App for use
in accessing the Service. Your use of the Website, App or Service does
not grant you any right, license or permission of any kind to reproduce
or use lufluf’s intellectual property.</p>

<p><B>User Feedback and Content Submissions</B></p>

<p>lufluf welcomes your feedback, but if you send us or post or embed on
the Website, App or via any Service, any feedback, messages or comments;
your creative or original concepts or ideas; any content, data, text,
photographs, graphics or other materials; or any confidential,
proprietary or other information (“Submissions”), you represent and
warrant to lufluf that you either own the Submission or have the right
to grant lufluf the license described below. lufluf does not claim
to own such Submission, only the rights you have licensed to us.</p>
<p>You agree that in making a Submission, lufluf shall not be required to
compensate you for any such license or Submission, that any such
Submission shall not be considered confidential or non&#45;public once
submitted to lufluf, and that lufluf alone is free to decide whether
or not to post or use the Submission. In the event a Submission is
posted or used via the Service, you acknowledge and agree that the
Submission and its contents become publicly available and, as set forth
below, can be used by others. Further, by providing a Submission to luf
luf via the Website, App or otherwise, you: &#40;a&#41; agree not to make any
Submission that violates in any way the Terms of Service; &#40;b&#41;
automatically grant lufluf a perpetual, worldwide, unlimited,
irrevocable, transferable, assignable, sub-licenseable license to use
the Submission, and exercise all copyright, publicity and other rights
with respect to any such Submission; &#40;c&#41; subject to existing laws, waive
any moral rights you or your licensors have in any such Submission; and
&#40;d&#41; agree to pay for all fees, royalties, or other costs and expenses
claimed by any third party arising out of you making any Submission. You
also grant each user of the Service a perpetual, worldwide,
non&#45;exclusive license to access your Submission through the Service, and
to use, reproduce, collect, distribute, share, display and perform such
Submission as permitted through the Service and under these Terms of
Service.</p>
<p>lufluf reserves the right to remove content at any time with or
without notice. Inappropriate content is not permitted on the Website or
App and will be removed. Inappropriate content includes but is not
limited to: firearms, alcohol, illegal drugs and drug paraphernalia,
tobacco and tobacco products, adult or pornographic material, offensive
material, and obscene material.</p>

<p><B>Termination</B></p>

<p>lufluf shall have the right to terminate your use of the Website, App
and/or your registration privileges at any time for any reason,
including, but not limited to, your breach of these Terms of Services,
or your violation of any law, including, without limitation, violations
of our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights
of a third party, or violations of other applicable laws and
regulations. Following any such termination, lufluf shall have no
further obligations, responsibilities, or liabilities to you or any
third party. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained herein,
in the event that lufluf terminates your use rights, lufluf shall in
no way be precluded from pursuing any and all of its additional rights
and remedies, either at law or in equity, for any claims, damages,
awards, costs and liabilities occasioned by such breach or violation.</p>

<p><B>Linking and Third Party Content</B></p>

<p>The Website, App and Service may contain links to third–party websites
not under our control or operation. lufluf or users may provide any
such links only as a convenience; lufluf does not endorse and is not
responsible for or have control over the contents of any linked site or
any link contained in a linked site. The Website and/or App may contain
news, advertisements, content, image and information published by
various third–party providers. Use of any such third–party content
may be conditioned upon such third party’s terms and conditions. You
are solely responsible for protecting yourself, your device, and your
systems from worms, viruses, Trojan horses and any other harmful
content.</p>

<p><B>Copyright Infringement</B></p>

<p>We respects copyright law and has a policy that provides for the
termination in appropriate circumstances of registered member who
repeatedly infringe or are believed to be repeatedly infringing the
rights of copyright holders.</p>
<p>If you believe that your copyrighted work has been copied in a way that
constitutes copyright infringement and is accessible on lufluf, please
notify lufluf&#39;s copyright agent at support&#64;qiito.com.sg When
filing your report, please provide the following information below:</p>

<p> * An electronic or physical signature of a person authorized to act on
       behalf of the copyright owner;</p>

<p> * Identification of the copyrighted work that you claim has been
       infringed;</p>

<p> * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing and
       where it is located on lufluf;</p>

<p> * Information reasonably sufficient to permit lufluf to contact you,
      such as your address, telephone number, and, e-mail address;</p>

<p> * A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material
       in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner,
       its agent, or law; and</p>

<p> * A statement, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information
       is accurate, and that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to
       act on behalf of the owner.</p>

<p>Once proper, bona fide infringement notification is received, it is our
policy:</p>


<p> * To remove or disable access to the infringing material;</p>

<p> * To notify the content provider, member or user that we have removed or
       disabled access to the material;</p>

<p> * That repeat offenders will have the infringing material removed from the
       system and that we will terminate such content provider’s, member’s
       or user’s access to the lufluf.</p>

<p><B>Limitation of Liability</B></p>

<p>lufluf shall not be liable to you, and you shall be solely
responsible, for the selection, use, and suitability of the Website, App
and the information, content, merchandise and experiences provided via
the Website and/or App. lufluf shall not be liable to you for any
direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, punitive, or
consequential or any other damages in connection with your use of the
Website or App, or purchase or use of products, merchandise, or
experiences via the Website or App, including, but not limited to, loss
of or damage to data or loss of or damage to information, personal
injury or property damage, however caused, whether based on contract,
tort, warranty, or other legal theory, even if lufluf has been
informed in advance of the possibility of such damages and/or such
damages could have been reasonably foreseen by lufluf. regardless of
whether any remedy set forth herein fails of its essential purpose.</p>
Sales, Custom and Value-added taxes
<p>In an effort to remain compliant with respective consumer legislations,
we strongly encourage our merchants as well as our end customers to
maintain good standing with respect to custom and value-added taxes or
VAT, where applicable.</p>
<p>Due to separate and applicable tax jurisdictions, the end customers’
purchases may be subject to specific sales, custom or value-added taxes,
and the shipping time and associated cost may increase.</p>


 </body></html>]]></string>

    <!--membership-->
    <string name="member_tile_heading">UPGRADE YOUR MEMBERSHIP NOW </string>
    <string name="join_membership_now"> &amp; enjoy attractive member discount!</string>

    <!--Membership Details-->
    <string name="member">Member</string>
    <string name="popular">POPULAR</string>
    <string name="collect_store">COLLECT AT STORE</string>


</resources>